smaller group and they look
at them,
they do not attempt to change
the
situation.
So in the northern states and
in
many of the parts of the
country,
they are bandits.
If the larger majority close
their eyes,
they don't do anything,
they just cross their fingers
and fold their arms.
They do not do anything to
it.
The Prophet said, Allah will
send a
punishment that will go
around everybody.
If a people, you are in a
community, some people are
committing evil and
you keep quiet,
Allah will send down the
punishment and
it will go around everybody.
Both those who are directly
involved and
those who have refused to do
anything.
In our religion, Islam,
it is prohibited that we see
evil
and we refuse to do anything.
You refuse to do anything.
You look away and see if it
does not concern you.
Look at the various young
people in
the society today, upon Yahu,
upon alcohol, upon various
kinds of deviations and then
you sit
down, you refuse to do
anything.